import '../classes/quiz_class.dart';

List<QuizQuestion> onePieceQuestions = [
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "At the introduction of Kaido, the “King Of Beasts” how many times had he been defeated and captured?",
      answer1: "Defeated 5 times and captured 33 times",
      answer2: "Defeated 7 times and captured 18 times",
      answer3: "Defeated 15 times and captured 40 times",
      answer4: "Defeated 20 times and captured 5 times",
      correctAnswer: "Defeated 7 times and captured 18 times"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Which one of the yonko members that didn't eat a devil fruit",
      answer1: "Big Mom",
      answer2: "Kaido",
      answer3: "Shanks",
      answer4: "White Beard",
      correctAnswer: "Shanks"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who kidnapped Nami and forced her to become a cartographer?",
      answer1: "Eric",
      answer2: "Pisaro",
      answer3: "Buggy",
      answer4: "Arlong",
      correctAnswer: "Arlong"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who hugs Tony Tony Chopper and cries after bringing back the Amiudake mushroom?",
      answer1: "Hiriluk",
      answer2: "Kureha",
      answer3: "Dalton",
      answer4: "Majed Deuce",
      correctAnswer: "Hiriluk"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Which food does Luffy dislike the most?",
      answer1: "Cherry Pie",
      answer2: "Rum Ice Cream",
      answer3: "Deviled Eggs",
      answer4: "Pocky",
      correctAnswer: "Cherry Pie"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What finishing technique does Jinbei use to defeat Big Mom?",
      answer1: "Kairagi Glaze",
      answer2: "Gomu Gomu no red Hawk",
      answer3: "Shoulder Throw",
      answer4: "Vagabond Drill",
      correctAnswer: "Vagabond Drill"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "How did Luffy get the scar under his eye?",
      answer1: "His Grandfather",
      answer2: "By Himself",
      answer3: "Protecting his crew",
      answer4: "Attacked when he was a child",
      correctAnswer: "By Himself"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Which young girl would Usopp stories of adventure to and entertain as a child?",
      answer1: "Yuuki",
      answer2: "Kaya",
      answer3: "Kiki",
      answer4: "Yuna",
      correctAnswer: "Kaya"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Going Merry was destroyed and replaced with another ship. What is the name of this ship?",
      answer1: "Sunny Rise",
      answer2: "Sunny Sunshine",
      answer3: "Happy Days",
      answer4: "Thousand Sunny",
      correctAnswer: "Thousand Sunny"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Since Luffy is terrible at drawing. Who drew their Jolly Roger flag?",
      answer1: "Usopp",
      answer2: "Nami",
      answer3: "Zoro",
      answer4: "Sanji",
      correctAnswer: "Usopp"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who has refused to join the Seven Warlords of the Sea?",
      answer1: "Nekomamushi",
      answer2: "Izo",
      answer3: "Ace",
      answer4: "Zoro",
      correctAnswer: "Ace"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What did Trafalgar law present to the World Government?",
      answer1: "100 hearts",
      answer2: "150 ears",
      answer3: "1000 fingers",
      answer4: "200 brains",
      correctAnswer: "100 hearts"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Most of One Piece takes place on what ocean current?",
      answer1: "Acqua Laguna",
      answer2: "Down Wind",
      answer3: "East Blue",
      answer4: "Grand Line",
      correctAnswer: "Grand Line"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Porche is a member of which pirate crew?",
      answer1: "Black Cat Priates",
      answer2: "Bluejam Pirates",
      answer3: "Foxy Pirates",
      answer4: "Buggy Pirates",
      correctAnswer: "Foxy Pirates"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "In what village dojo did Roronoa Zoro train in?",
      answer1: "Shimotsuki Village",
      answer2: "Kuen Village",
      answer3: "Ina Village",
      answer4: "Foosha Village",
      correctAnswer: "Shimotsuki Village"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "How many families started the world government?",
      answer1: "20 families",
      answer2: "25 families",
      answer3: "30 families",
      answer4: "35 families",
      correctAnswer: "20 families"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Following the time skip, how many of the original Seven Warlords remained?",
      answer1: "Three",
      answer2: "Four",
      answer3: "Five",
      answer4: "Six",
      correctAnswer: "Four"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Sir Crocodile is the former president of which crime syndicate?",
      answer1: "Beasts Pirates",
      answer2: "Barouqe Works",
      answer3: "Ganzack Pirates",
      answer4: "God's Army",
      correctAnswer: "Barouqe Works"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is Sanji Vinsmoke’s favorite food?",
      answer1: "Konjack",
      answer2: "Spicy Smoke Sausage",
      answer3: "Ice Cream",
      answer4: "Spice Seafood Pasta",
      correctAnswer: "Spice Seafood Pasta"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Which of these characters don’t have Haoshoku Haki?",
      answer1: "Big Mom",
      answer2: "Pica",
      answer3: "Eustass Kid",
      answer4: "Doflamingo",
      correctAnswer: "Pica"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who said, 'Scars on the back are a swordsman’s shame'?",
      answer1: "Zoro",
      answer2: "Mihawk",
      answer3: "Law",
      answer4: "Shanks",
      correctAnswer: "Zoro"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who labels themselves the ace of CP7?",
      answer1: "Capote",
      answer2: "Wanze",
      answer3: "Charlotte Mont-d'Or",
      answer4: "Doha Ittanka II",
      correctAnswer: "Wanze"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "'Iron Man' Franky had the original name of what?",
      answer1: "Pandaman",
      answer2: "Mountain Ricky",
      answer3: "Sakushiba Kanishitoru",
      answer4: "Cutty Flame",
      correctAnswer: "Cutty Flame"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the capital city of the World Government?",
      answer1: "Enies Lobby",
      answer2: "Guanhao",
      answer3: "Marry Geoise",
      answer4: "Pangaea Castle",
      correctAnswer: "Marry Geoise"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Which character has used their boogers as an explosive?",
      answer1: "Ussop",
      answer2: "Mr.5",
      answer3: "Mr.9",
      answer4: "Ms.All Sunday",
      correctAnswer: "Mr.5"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "A Bible is carried around by which character?",
      answer1: "Bartholomew Kuma",
      answer2: "Monkey D.Dragon",
      answer3: "Dracula Mihawk",
      answer4: "Sabo",
      correctAnswer: "Bartholomew Kuma"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who had stolen a ship to live on because their house was burned down?",
      answer1: "Gol D.Roger",
      answer2: "Scopper Gaban",
      answer3: "Silvers Rayleigh",
      answer4: "Portgas D.Acw",
      correctAnswer: "Silvers Rayleigh"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who gave shanks the scar on his eye?",
      answer1: "Mihawk",
      answer2: "Kaido",
      answer3: "Black Beard",
      answer4: "White Beard",
      correctAnswer: "Black Beard"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "“I want to live! Take me out to sea with you!!” was said by which character?",
      answer1: "Chopper",
      answer2: "Nami",
      answer3: "Ussop",
      answer4: "Robin",
      correctAnswer: "Robin"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who is the Vice Warden of Impel Down?",
      answer1: "Shiryu",
      answer2: "Sukoshiba Kanishitoru",
      answer3: "Magellan",
      answer4: "Hannyabal",
      correctAnswer: "Hannyabal"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Franky changes his hairstyle by doing what?",
      answer1: "Pressing his nose",
      answer2: "Pressing his forehead",
      answer3: "Button on his sunglasses",
      answer4: "Pulling his finger",
      correctAnswer: "Pressing his nose"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "The One Piece world has its version of the Bermuda Triangle. What is theirs called?",
      answer1: "Devils Mist",
      answer2: "Badmans Triangle",
      answer3: "Florian Triangle",
      answer4: "Escutcheon Destroyer",
      correctAnswer: "Florian Triangle"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Luffy was faced with anger from which crew member when he made his announcement about parting with the Going Merry?",
      answer1: "Nami",
      answer2: "Zoro",
      answer3: "Robin",
      answer4: "Usopp",
      correctAnswer: "Usopp"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "The Marines have what at the bottom of their ships that allow them to cross the Calm Belts?",
      answer1: "Wapometal",
      answer2: "Seastone Lining",
      answer3: "Amber Lead",
      answer4: "Vearth",
      correctAnswer: "Seastone Lining"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Because of Sanji’s experience with Zeff he made a vow to never refuse food to someone starving. Sanji made true to this vow when he fed who?",
      answer1: "Gin",
      answer2: "Koza",
      answer3: "Hiriluk",
      answer4: "Catacombo",
      correctAnswer: "Gin"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "In the anime, Gol D. Roger was executed in which way?",
      answer1: "Decapitated",
      answer2: "Hung from the gallows",
      answer3: "Walked a plank",
      answer4: "Stabbed with two spears",
      correctAnswer: "Stabbed with two spears"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Which member of the Strawhat Pirates was the only one to have their bounty picture drawn?",
      answer1: "Usopp",
      answer2: "Zoro",
      answer3: "Sanji",
      answer4: "Chopper",
      correctAnswer: "Sanji"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Of The Straw Hat Grand Fleet, which pirate crew has a figurehead of Luffy at their bow?",
      answer1: "Ideo Pirates",
      answer2: "Happo Navy",
      answer3: "Beautiful Pirates",
      answer4: "Barto Club",
      correctAnswer: "Barto Club"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Zeus, the thundercloud, wears a hat of what color?",
      answer1: "Blue and Yellow",
      answer2: "Red and White",
      answer3: "Black and Green",
      answer4: "Orange and Pink",
      correctAnswer: "Red and White"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Throughout the series, luffy had six bounties including his current one. What is the sum of them?",
      answer1: "2.75 billion beri",
      answer2: "2.87 billion beri",
      answer3: "2.34 billion beri",
      answer4: "2.83 billion beri",
      correctAnswer: "2.83 billion beri"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Where was Gol D. Roger born?",
      answer1: "East Blue",
      answer2: "West Blue",
      answer3: "North Blue",
      answer4: "South Blue",
      correctAnswer: "East Blue"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who is Luffy's first main opponent?",
      answer1: "Arlong",
      answer2: "Alvida",
      answer3: "Akainu",
      answer4: "Buggy",
      correctAnswer: "Alvida"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Which of the following is not a type of Haki?",
      answer1: "Kenbunshoku - Observation",
      answer2: "Busoshoku - Armament",
      answer3: "Haoshoku - Conquerer's",
      answer4: "Kamishoku - Divinity",
      correctAnswer: "Kamishoku - Divinity"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who gave luffy his straw hat?",
      answer1: "garp",
      answer2: "shanks",
      answer3: "dragon",
      answer4: "ace",
      correctAnswer: "shanks"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "after how many years did luffy reunion with his crew",
      answer1: "one year",
      answer2: "two years",
      answer3: "three years",
      answer4: "four years",
      correctAnswer: "two years"
  ),
];

//45 questions